21publish.com 2007-12-11

# 21Publish – Multi-User Blogs for Business and Communities - Privacy policy

## 21Publish Privacy Policy

  * **1\. Privacy Policy**  
Your privacy is important to 21Publish. This statement describes 21Publish's privacy practices for its own Web site, as well as the Web sites 21Publish hosts for its customers, including what type of information is gathered and tracked, how the information is used, and with whom the information is shared. This privacy statement does not disclose how 21Publish's customers use data collected on Web sites that 21Publish hosts for them.
  * **2\. Personal Information**  
You can visit www.21publish.com or any 21Publish hosted Web site without telling us who you are and without revealing any information about yourself. However, to access certain portions of the Web site, you may have to submit information such as user-id and password, or to access some services we provide, you may have to give us personal information such as your name and address and e-mail.  
To access our services, we may ask you for your address and/or credit card information.
  * **3\. Information security and quality**  
We intend to protect the quality and integrity of your personally identifiable information. We have implemented appropriate physical, technical and organizational measures, such as using industry accepted encryption for transmission of credit card information, to help keep your information secure, accurate, current, and complete.
  * **4\. Web site traffic information**  
When you arrive at any 21Publish hosted Web site, we automatically receive the Web address of the site that you came from. We also collect information on which pages of our Web site you visit while you are on our hosted site, the type of browser you use and the times you access our hosted sites. We use this information only to try to better understand visitor preferences and to manage the load on our servers. 
  * **5\. Cookies**  
We sometimes use cookies to collect anonymous information from visits to our sites to help us provide better service. We may use this data to analyze trends and statistics and to help us provide better customer service, but we do so in ways that keep the information anonymous. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your system. You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. You can also set your browser to turn off cookies. If you do so, however, some areas of some sites may not function properly. 
  * **6\. Disclosure to third parties**  
We will only share personally identifiable information with a third party if and when the individual submitting this information has permitted us to do so, or if we are required by law to do so. 
  * **7\. Email tools**  
21Publish offers its customers sophisticated email marketing tools. 21Publish itself adheres to a strict anti-spam policy, making it easy for subscribers to unsubscribe. 21Publish also provides Web site visitors who have created an account with email marketing tools. 
  * **8\. Personalized Web pages**  
21Publish enables its customers to allow their constituents to create personalized Web pages. 21Publish also enables customers to allow constituents to create Web content (including email) that bring visitors to these personalized Web pages. Such personal Web pages as well as the customer associated with these pages are readily identifiable. By clicking on a link and going to a personal Web page you are agreeing to let 21Publish collect information about your session visits. We use this information, and also provide it to our customers, for aggregate statistical analysis only. If a visitor provides personal information on these Web pages, then we make this information available only to the customer associated with the pages. 
  * **9\. Links to Other Web Sites**  
21Publish hosted sites contain links to other Web sites. 21Publish is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
